Guide to the Brand Blanshard Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- General Files, 1915-1989; Series I; 14.25 linear feet (35 boxes)
  - American Humanist Association, 1973-1986 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - American Mercury, 1945-1948 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - American Oxonian, 1957-1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - American Philosophical Association, 1942-1986 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - American Philosophical Association. Commission on the Function of Philosophy in Liberal Education, 1943-1944 May (Box 2, Folder 26)
    General note
    See also: box 17, folder 381
  - American Philosophical Association. Commission on the Function of Philosophy in Liberal Education, 1944 June (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - American Philosophical Association. Commission on the Function of Philosophy in Liberal Education, 1944-1946 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - American Philosophical Association. Eastern Division, 1945-1965 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - American Philosophical Society, 1948-1989 (Box 2, Folder 30-31)
  - American Philosophical Society: meeting notices; lists of members, 1948-1975 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - American Philosophical Society: meeting notices; lists of members, 1976-1984 (Box 2, Folder 33-34)
  - American Society for Psychical Research, 1956-1969 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - American Theological Society, 1955-1987 (Box 3, Folder 36-37)
  - Anderson, Alan R., 1959-1966, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Anderson, James F., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Anderson, Troyer, 1944, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Anshen, Ruth, 1960, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Aristotelian Society, 1950-1988 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Armstrong, Annie Laurie, 1966-1982 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1960-1964 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Athenaeum, 1950-1958 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Atkins, Elisha, 1966-1984, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Aurelian Honor Society, 1949-1987 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Avery, George, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Aydelotte, Frank, 1935-1955 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    See also: box 27, folders 635 See also: box 31, folder 725
  - Aydelotte, William O., 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Ba-Bi (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Bl-Bo (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Br-By (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Baer, Ann, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Bagley, Charles, 1941-1956 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Bailey, Joan E., 1964-1971 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Bainton, Roland, 1967-1980 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Ball State Teachers College, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Ballard, Kaith, 1959-1966 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Barnes, Albert, 1919-1920 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Bartle, Glenn and Wanda, 1953-1986 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Basic Books, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Baum, Maurice, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Baylis, Charles, 1946-1960 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Beacon Press, 1950-1984 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Beardsley, Monroe and Elizabeth, 1936-1982, undated (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Bearn, Alexander and Margaret, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Beck, Maximilian, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Beck, Robert N., 1970-1980 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    See also: box 18, folder 413
  - Becker, Lawrence, 1971-1972, undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Belsey, Andrew, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Belsey, Elizabeth, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Bennett, Stephen, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Benton, Mrs. George O., 1931-1941 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Berndtson, Arthur, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Bertanni, David, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Bertocci, Peter, 1946-1987 (Box 4, Folder 77-78)
  - Bethany College, 1962-1969 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Bharati, Agehananda, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Bhattacharya, Devaprasad, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Bhattacharya, Usha, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Bixler, Seelye and Mary, 1918-1983 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Black, Mary, 1942-1961 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Blackwell's, 1968-1984 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Blanshard, Bailey, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Blanshard, Beatrice Mayer, 1980-1987 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    See also: box 7, folder 133
  - Blanshard, Clemency, 1956-1987 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Blanshard, Emily, 1926-1939 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Blanshard, Frances Bradshaw, 1918 March-December (Box 6, Folder 90-94)
  - Blanshard, Frances Bradshaw, Circa 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Blanshard, Frances Bradshaw, 1919 January-August (Box 5, Folder 96-102)
  - Blanshard, Frances Bradshaw, Circa (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Blanshard, Frances Bradshaw, 1929 August-December (Box 5, Folder 104-107)
  - Blanshard, Frances Bradshaw, Circa 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Blanshard, Frances Bradshaw, 1930 January-March (Box 5, Folder 109-110)
  - Blanshard, Frances Bradshaw, 1930 May-August (Box 6, Folder 111-114)
  - Blanshard, Frances Bradshaw, Circa 1931-1933 (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Blanshard, Frances Bradshaw, 1935-1940 (Box 6, Folder 116-118)
  - Blanshard, Frances Bradshaw, Circa 1931-1941 (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Blanshard, Frances Bradshaw, 1942-1945, 1948-1959, circa 1961-1966, undated (Box 6, Folder 120-123)
  - Blanshard, Judy, 1960-1988 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Blanshard, Luke and Sarah, 1967-1988 (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Blanshard, Orminda Adams, 1918-1920, undated (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Blanshard, Paul, 1915-1923, circa 1925-1979 (Box 7, Folder 127-136)
  - Blanshard, Paul, Jr., 1940-1988 (Box 7, Folder 137-141)
  - Blanshard, Peter, 1963-1985 (Box 8, Folder 142)
  - Blanshard, Roberta Yerkes, 1950-1989 (Box 8, Folder 143)
  - Blanshard, Rufus, 1935-1949, 1951-1988 (Box 8, Folder 144-147)
  - Boas, George, 1961-1980 (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - Boehm, John, 1960, undated (Box 8, Folder 149)
  - Bonner, Campbell, 1948-1983 (Box 8, Folder 150)
  - Boring, Edwin G., 1961-1971 (Box 8, Folder 151)
  - Boston University, 1949, 1960, 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - Bosworth, Wayne and Marguerite, 1963-1981 (Box 8, Folder 153)
  - Bowdoin College, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 154)
  - Bowman, Carroll R., 1966-1971 (Box 8, Folder 155)
  - Bradley, F. H., 1920 (Box 8, Folder 156)
  - Bradshaw, Margaret, 1918-1930 (Box 8, Folder 157)
  - Branden, Nathaniel, 1962-1966 (Box 8, Folder 158)
  - Brandt, Richard, 1937-1979 (Box 8, Folder 159)
  - Braybrook, Geoffrey, 1957-1970, undated (Box 8, Folder 160)
  - Brecher, Edward M., 1936-1971 (Box 8, Folder 161)
  - Bredenburg, Paul A., 1957-1969 (Box 8, Folder 162)
  - Brightman, Edgar S., 1940-1948 (Box 9, Folder 163)
  - British Academy, 1951-1983, undated (Box 9, Folder 164)
  - Brodie, Philip, 1973-1977 (Box 9, Folder 165)
  - Brown, Stuart, 1946, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 166)
  - Brown University, 1963-1973 (Box 9, Folder 167)
  - Broyer, John A., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 168)
  - Brumbaugh, Robert, 1954-1988, undated (Box 9, Folder 169)
  - Bryn Mawr College, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 170)
  - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1951, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 171)
  - Bucknell University, 1948-1958 (Box 9, Folder 172)
  - Burgess, James, 1981-1985 (Box 9, Folder 173)
  - Burhoe, Ralph W., 1957-1972 (Box 9, Folder 174)
  - Burk, Harold, 1961-1988 (Box 9, Folder 175)
  - Burkhardt, Frederick, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 176)
  - Burtt, Edwin, 1960-1987 (Box 9, Folder 177)
  - Butterfield, Victor L., 1950-1967 (Box 9, Folder 178)
  - Ca-Cl (Box 9, Folder 179)
  - Co-Cu (Box 9, Folder 180)
  - Cadbury, Warden, 1950-1952, undated (Box 9, Folder 181)
  - Cadigan, Robert, 1937-1956 (Box 9, Folder 182)
  - Calhoun, Mary, 1957-1985 (Box 9, Folder 183)
  - Camber, Bruce, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 184)
  - Cambridge University Library, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 185)
  - Campbell, Charles Arthur, 1952-1974 (Box 9, Folder 186)
  - Campbell, James, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 187)
  - Campbell, Richard, 1961-1988 (Box 9, Folder 188)
  - Carleton College, 1954-1973 (Box 9, Folder 189)
  - Carlin, William, 1949-1951 (Box 9, Folder 190)
  - Carmichael, Oliver C., 1920-1948 (Box 9, Folder 191)
  - Carnap, Rudolph, 1948-1960, undated (Box 9, Folder 192)
  - Carrell, Demaris Affleck, 1944-1988 (Box 10, Folder 193-194)
  - Carrell-Smith, Kimberly, 1975-1987 (Box 10, Folder 195)
  - Carritt, Edgar, 1925-1965, undated (Box 10, Folder 196-198)
  - Castaglione, Robert, 1981-1988 (Box 10, Folder 199)
  - Castell, Alburey, 1942-1988 (Box 10, Folder 200)
  - Catholic University of America, 1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 201)
  - Cato Institute, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 202)
  - Center for Advanced Study in Religion and Science, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 203)
    See also: box 9, folder 174
  - Center for American Studies
    See: box 12, folder 247
  - Center for Dewey Studies, 1967-1985 (Box 10, Folder 204-205)
  - Center for Philosophic Exchange, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 206)
  - Chalfan, David, 1964-1988 (Box 11, Folder 207-210)
  - Chang, Wyzie S., 1932-1974 (Box 11, Folder 211)
  - Chappell, Vere, 1953-1969 (Box 11, Folder 212)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons, 1953-1968 (Box 11, Folder 213)
  - Chatham College, 1964-1973 (Box 11, Folder 214)
  - Chin Cheng, Maggie, 1959, undated (Box 11, Folder 215)
  - Chisholm, Roderick, 1946-1960 (Box 11, Folder 216)
  - Chrismer, R. Leslie, 1935-1977, undated (Box 11, Folder 217)
  - Clark, John A., 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 218)
  - Clayton, Marcus, 1964-1971 (Box 11, Folder 219-220)
  - Cochran, Betty and Frank, 1963-1988 (Box 11, Folder 221)
  - Cocutz, John, 1948-1955 (Box 11, Folder 222)
  - Cohen, Robert S., 1949-1985 (Box 11, Folder 223)
  - Colgate-Rochester Divinity School, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 224)
  - College of Puget Sound, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 225)
  - College of Wooster, 1966-1987 (Box 11, Folder 226)
  - Collier Books, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 227)
  - Collier's Encyclopedia, 1946-1948, 1960, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 228)
  - Columbia University, 1918-1983, undated (Box 12, Folder 229)
  - Columbia University Press, 1948-1980 (Box 12, Folder 230)
  - Committee for the Scientific Investigation of Claims of the Paranormal, 1975-1981 June-Dec, 1982-1986, n.d (Box 12, Folder 231-236)
  - Committee to Defend America by Aiding the Allies. Swarthmore Chapter, Circa 1940 (Box 12, Folder 237)
  - Concord College, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 238)
  - Conference on Methods in Philosophy and the Sciences, 1941-1942, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 239)
  - Conference on Science, Philosophy, and Religion, 1945-1950 (Box 12, Folder 240)
  - Conference on the Scientific Spirit and Democratic Faith (Box 12, Folder 241)
  - Congresso National de Filosofia, 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 242)
  - Connecticut Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1948-1987, undated (Box 12, Folder 243)
  - Coppock, Joseph D., 1968-1986 (Box 12, Folder 244)
  - Corkey, R., 1960-1966 (Box 12, Folder 245)
  - Corwin, Wallace G. and Margaret, 1945-1969 (Box 12, Folder 246)
  - Couch, William T., 1963-1982 (Box 12, Folder 247)
  - Council for Democratic and Secular Humanism
    See: box 1, folder 3
  - Council for Philosophical Studies, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 248)
  - Cowgill, Kathryn
    See: box 16, folder 365
  - Cox, Edward and Jane, 1943-1985, undated (Box 12, Folder 249)
  - Cramer, Maurice, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 250)
  - Crane, Charles, 1936-1945 (Box 12, Folder 251)
  - Cranston, Maurice, 1947-1952 (Box 12, Folder 252)
  - Creel, Richard E., 1968-1981 (Box 12, Folder 253)
  - Currie, Cecil, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 254)
  - D (Box 12, Folder 255)
  - Dade, James, 1974, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 256)
  - Daedalus, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 257)
  - D'Agostino, Matthew, 1964-1976 (Box 13, Folder 258)
  - Darbishire, Helen, 1926-1961 (Box 13, Folder 259)
  - Darshana, 1962-1963, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 260)
  - Davis, Philip E., 1957-1974 (Box 13, Folder 261)
  - Davis, Sydney, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 262)
  - Day, Patrick, 1950-1953 (Box 13, Folder 263)
  - Debbins, William, 1964-1970 (Box 13, Folder 264)
  - De George, Richard T., 1960-1973 (Box 13, Folder 265)
  - De Laguna, Grace, 1934-1978 (Box 13, Folder 266)
    See also: box 15, folder 322
  - Delsård-Ransen, Paul, 1953-1958, undated (Box 13, Folder 267)
  - De Moor, Leonard, 1936-1970 (Box 13, Folder 268)
  - Dennes, William, 1942-1947 (Box 13, Folder 269)
  - d'Entrèves, Alexander P., 1958-1960 (Box 13, Folder 270)
  - DeVane, William C. and Mabel, 1957-1969 (Box 13, Folder 271)
  - Dewey, John, 1918-1952 (Box 13, Folder 272)
  - Dewey, Robert E., 1964 (Box 13, Folder 273)
  - Dickinson College, 1963-1978 (Box 13, Folder 274)
  - Dickie, Edgar P., 1948-1980 (Box 13, Folder 275)
  - Dickoff, James, 1960-1971 (Box 13, Folder 276)
  - Diemert, Gerome, 1953-1955 (Box 13, Folder 277)
  - Dietrichson, Paul, 1950-1968 (Box 13, Folder 278)
  - Dominguez, Diego, 1961-1967 (Box 13, Folder 279)
  - Douglas, Christine, 1959-1988 (Box 13, Folder 280)
  - Ducasse, Curt John, 1940-1967 (Box 13, Folder 281)
  - Dupré, Louis, 1972-1980, undated (Box 13, Folder 282)
  - Dydo, Joan, 1983-1987 (Box 13, Folder 283)
  - E (Box 13, Folder 284)
  - Ecklund, John and Constance, 1983-1988, undated (Box 13, Folder 285)
  - Edwards, Paul, 1956-1975 (Box 13, Folder 286)
    See also: box 14, folder 293
  - Eliot, T. S., 1951,1976 (Box 13, Folder 287)
  - Elizabethan Club, 1952-1984 (Box 13, Folder 288)
  - Emmet, Dorothy, 1952-1981, undated (Box 13, Folder 289)
  - Enck, Graves, 1985-1988 (Box 13, Folder 290)
  - Encyclopedia Americana, 1959-1963, undated (Box 13, Folder 291)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1969-1973 (Box 14, Folder 292)
  - Encyclopedia of Philosophy, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 293)
  - Engle, Paul, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 294)
  - Erba, Paula A., 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 295)
  - Ewell, John Woodruff, 1986-1988 (Box 14, Folder 296)
  - Ewing, Alfred Cyril, 1943-1973 (Box 14, Folder 297)
  - Fa-F1 (Box 14, Folder 298)
  - Fo-Fu (Box 14, Folder 299)
  - Fang, Joongniop, 1949-1951 (Box 14, Folder 300)
  - Federal Union, 1953-1986 (Box 14, Folder 301)
  - Fédération Internationale des Sociétés de Philosophie, 1953-1965 (Box 14, Folder 302)
  - Feigl, Herbert, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 303)
  - Fellowship of Religious Humanists, 1968-1985 (Box 14, Folder 304)
  - Ferguson, A. S., 1947-1958 (Box 14, Folder 305)
  - Ferré, Frederick, 1964-1987 (Box 14, Folder 306)
  - Feuer, Lewis S., 1965-1984 (Box 14, Folder 307)
  - Firth, Roderick, 1960-1964 (Box 14, Folder 308)
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield, Circa 1928-1954 undated (Box 14, Folder 309-310)
  - Fitch, Frederic Brenton, 1947-1988 (Box 14, Folder 311)
  - Flew, Antony, Circa 1964 (Box 14, Folder 312)
  - Flora, Wesley, 1944-1950 (Box 14, Folder 313)
  - Fogelin, Robert J., 1959-1966 (Box 14, Folder 314)
  - Ford, Lewis S., 1975 (Box 14, Folder 315)
  - Forscher, Louise, 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 316)
  - Frank L. Weil Institute, 1961, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 317)
  - Fraser, David W., 1984-1988 (Box 15, Folder 318)
  - Free Inquiry, 1980-1987 (Box 15, Folder 319)
    See also: box 1, folder 3
  - Freeman, Eugene
    See: box 23, folders 542 See: box 25, folder 582
  - Friend, Theodore, 1973-1981 (Box 15, Folder 320)
  - Friends Journal, 1962-1981 (Box 15, Folder 321)
  - Fullerton Club, 1934-1949 (Box 15, Folder 322)
  - Furniss, E. S., 1945-1960 (Box 15, Folder 323)
  - Fussell, Morris and Frances, 1966-1975 (Box 15, Folder 324)
  - Fyfe, W. H., 1922-1934 (Box 15, Folder 325)
  - Ga-Go (Box 15, Folder 326)
  - Gr-Gy (Box 15, Folder 327)
  - Garelick, Herbert M., 1957-1959 (Box 15, Folder 328)
  - Garver, Newton, 1985-1988 (Box 15, Folder 329)
  - Geibel, Larry, 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 330)
  - George Allen and Unwin, 1948-1988 (Box 15, Folder 331)
  - George Allen and Unwin: Nature of Thought, 1939-1963 (Box 15, Folder 332)
  - George Allen and Unwin: Reason and Analysis, 1959-1966 (Box 15, Folder 333)
  - George Allen and Unwin: Reason and Belief, 1966-1983 (Box 15, Folder 334)
  - George Allen and Unwin: Reason and Goodness, 1959-1965 (Box 15, Folder 335)
  - George Allen and Unwin: royalties, 1949-1981 (Box 15, Folder 336-337)
  - Ghosh, J. C., 1947 (Box 15, Folder 338)
  - Gibson, A. Boyce, 1958-1960 (Box 15, Folder 339)
  - Gilliams, Luvenia Hardison, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 340)
  - Gilliland, Robert, 1985-1988 (Box 15, Folder 341)
  - Goddard, Harold and Margaret, 1937-1975 (Box 15, Folder 342)
  - Gotshalk, D. Walter, 1955-1966 (Box 15, Folder 343)
  - Gotthelf, Allan, 1963-1974 (Box 15, Folder 344)
  - Graduate Philosophy Club, 1947-1959 (Box 15, Folder 345)
  - Gray, Elva, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 346)
  - Greene, Theodore, 1946-1969 (Box 16, Folder 347)
  - Grier, Philip T., 1985-1988 (Box 16, Folder 348)
  - Grinnell College, 1961-1967 (Box 16, Folder 349)
  - Griswold, Whitney and Mary, 1952-1966 (Box 16, Folder 350)
  - Grolier, Inc., 1960-1964 (Box 16, Folder 351)
  - Gross, Mark, 1941-1988 (Box 16, Folder 352)
  - Grünbaum, Adolf, 1947-1985 (Box 16, Folder 353)
  - Grunebaum, L. H., 1947-1972 (Box 16, Folder 354)
  - Gutmann, James, 1951-1983 (Box 16, Folder 355)
  - Ha (Box 16, Folder 356)
  - He-Hi (Box 16, Folder 357)
  - Ho-Hu (Box 16, Folder 358)
  - Hahn, Lewis E., 1966-1987 (Box 16, Folder 359)
  - Hallberg, Fred W., 1963-1970 (Box 16, Folder 360)
  - Hallman, L. Robert, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 361)
  - Hancock, Roger N., 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 362)
  - Hanson, Norwood Russell, 1950-1966 (Box 16, Folder 363)
  - Harbert, David L., 1960-1962, undated (Box 16, Folder 364)
  - Harding, Kathryn, 1985-1987 (Box 16, Folder 365)
  - Hare, Peter H., 1970-1987 (Box 16, Folder 366)
  - Harper and Row, 1945-1973 (Box 16, Folder 367)
  - Harries, Karsten, 1957-1989 (Box 16, Folder 368)
  - Harris, Errol, 1950-1987 (Box 16, Folder 369-370)
  - Hartman, Robert S., 1946-1960 (Box 16, Folder 371)
  - Hartzell, Karl Drew, 1967-1970 (Box 16, Folder 372)
  - Harvard University, 1945-1970 (Box 16, Folder 373)
  - Harvard University. Graduate School, 1919-1921 (Box 16, Folder 374)
  - Harvard University Press, 1960, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 375)
  - Hausman, Carl R., 1968-1980 (Box 16, Folder 376)
  - Hazelett, S. Richard, 1982-1985 (Box 17, Folder 377)
  - Healey, Francis G., 1941-1984 (Box 17, Folder 378)
  - Hempel, Carl, 1947-1948, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 379)
  - Hempel, Peter, 1949-1975, undated (Box 17, Folder 380)
  - Hendel, Charles W., 1943-1983 (Box 17, Folder 381-384)
  - Hick, John H., 1962-1963, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 385)
  - Hill, Thomas E., 1951-1968 (Box 17, Folder 386)
  - Hiss, Alger, 1948-1976, undated (Box 17, Folder 387)
  - Hitchcock, Margaret, 1971-1985 (Box 17, Folder 388)
  - Hocking, Richard, 1966-1974 (Box 17, Folder 389)
  - Hocking, William Ernest, 1929-1964 (Box 17, Folder 390-391)
  - Hollins College, 1936-1949 (Box 17, Folder 392)
  - Holmes, Rebecca Webb, 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 393)
  - Holmes, Roger W., 1945-1964 (Box 17, Folder 394)
  - Holton, Gerald, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 395)
  - Hook, Sidney, 1943-1985, undated (Box 17, Folder 396)
  - Hopkins, Jeannette, 1957-1962 (Box 17, Folder 397-398)
  - Hopkins, Jeannette, 1963-1988 (Box 18, Folder 399-400)
  - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 401)
  - Howe, Leroy T., 1967-1969 (Box 18, Folder 402)
  - Howie, John, 1967-1988 (Box 18, Folder 403-405)
  - Humanist (Box 18, Folder 403-405)
    General
    See: box 1, folder 20
  - Humanities Press, 1963-1987 (Box 18, Folder 406)
  - Humphrey, Richard, 1942-1947, undated (Box 18, Folder 407)
  - Humphrey, Sylvia, 1967-1973, undated (Box 18, Folder 408)
  - Hunt, Everett, 1955-1983 (Box 18, Folder 409-410)
  - Hurlburt, Nancy, 1980-1988 (Box 18, Folder 411)
  - I (Box 18, Folder 412)
  - Idealistic Studies, 1971-1991 (Box 18, Folder 413)
  - Indiana University, 1960-1964 (Box 18, Folder 414)
  - Indiana University Press, 1954-1988 (Box 18, Folder 415)
  - Ingardia, Richard, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 416)
  - Institut International de Philosophie, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 417)
  - Institute on Religion in an Age of Science, 1957-1974 (Box 18, Folder 418)
  - Inter-American Conference of Philosophy, 1943-1947 (Box 19, Folder 419)
  - International Congress of Philosophy, 1944-1963 (Box 19, Folder 420)
  - J (Box 19, Folder 421)
  - Jablecki, Lawrence T., 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 422)
  - Jacobs, Norman, 1958-1961 (Box 19, Folder 423)
  - Jaffe, Raymond, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 424)
  - James, Patricia
    See: box 13, folder 276
  - Jansen, William, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 425)
  - Jenkins, Elsa, 1966-1978 (Box 19, Folder 426)
  - Jenkins, Iredell, 1948-1950 (Box 19, Folder 427)
  - Jesse Holmes Memorial, 1942-1946 (Box 19, Folder 428)
  - Joachim, Harold, 1917-1929, undated (Box 19, Folder 429)
  - John Dewey Society, 1954-1960, undated (Box 19, Folder 430)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1924-1985 (Box 19, Folder 431)
  - Johnson, Oliver, 1953-1987 (Box 19, Folder 432)
  - Jones, Howard M., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 433)
  - Jones, Thomas H., 1974-1978 (Box 19, Folder 434)
  - Jones, William Thomas, 1933-1967 (Box 19, Folder 435)
  - Joseph, Horace William Brindley, 1920-1943 (Box 19, Folder 436)
  - K (Box 19, Folder 437)
  - Kalow, Gert, 1953-1973 (Box 19, Folder 438)
  - Kane, Thomas S., 1963, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 439)
  - Kansas City Regional Council for Higher Education, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 440)
  - Kansas State College, 1967-1972 (Box 19, Folder 441)
  - Karalis, Nicholas, 1955-1969 (Box 19, Folder 442)
  - Kearns, John, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 443)
  - Keene, Calvin, 1947, 1966-1988 (Box 19, Folder 444)
  - Keener, Carl S., 1986-1988 (Box 19, Folder 445)
  - Keeny, Spurgeon M., 1979-1982 (Box 19, Folder 446)
  - Kegley, Charles W., 1964-1972 (Box 19, Folder 447)
  - Kelner, Nancy Blanshard, 1967-1987 (Box 19, Folder 448)
  - Kemp, John, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 449)
  - Kendig, Dennis, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 450)
  - Kennick, W.E., 1963-1965 (Box 19, Folder 451)
  - Kenyon College, 1961, 1975-1976, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 452)
  - Knox, John, 1964-1975 (Box 20, Folder 453)
  - Knox, Thomas Malcolm, 1949-1963 (Box 20, Folder 454)
    See also: box 30, folder 719
  - Knox, Thomas Malcolm, 1964-1980 (Box 20, Folder 455)
  - Kohák, Erazim, 1983-1988 (Box 20, Folder 456)
  - Korzybski, Alfred, 1933-1949 (Box 20, Folder 457)
  - Kraft, Julius, 1945-1960 (Box 20, Folder 458)
  - Kruse, Cornelius, 1938-1979 (Box 20, Folder 459)
  - Kuhn, Helmut, 1942-1955 (Box 20, Folder 460)
  - Kuklick, Bruce, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 461)
  - Kuntz, Paul Grimley, 1961-1979 (Box 20, Folder 462)
  - Kurtz, Paul
    See: box 1, folder 3 See: box 1, folder 20 See: box 12, folders 231 See: box 15, folder 319
  - La-Le (Box 20, Folder 463)
  - Li-Lu (Box 20, Folder 464)
  - Lachs, John, 1958-1987 (Box 20, Folder 465)
  - Lamont, Corliss, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 466)
  - Landis, Kendall, 1976-1989 (Box 20, Folder 467)
  - Larson, Cedric A., 1962, 1971-1987 (Box 20, Folder 468)
  - Lascola, Russell A., 1969-1976 (Box 20, Folder 469)
  - Lascombe, Alice, 1942-1976 (Box 20, Folder 470)
  - Latham, Robert, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 471)
  - Lazerowitz, Morris and Alice, 1948-1979 (Box 21, Folder 472)
  - Lazerowitz, Morris and Alice, 1981-1988 (Box 21, Folder 473)
  - Lazo, John, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 474)
  - League for Industrial Democracy, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 475)
  - Lean, Martin E., 1966-1974 (Box 21, Folder 476)
  - Le Boutillier, Cornelia, 1947-1948 (Box 21, Folder 477)
  - Lehner, Felix, 1957-1988 (Box 21, Folder 478)
  - Lerner, Marguerite and Seth, 1985-1988 (Box 21, Folder 479)
  - Leslie, John, 1969-1978 (Box 21, Folder 480)
  - Lewis, Clarence, 1934-1941 (Box 21, Folder 481)
  - Lewis, Hywel D., 1956-1988 (Box 21, Folder 482)
  - Lindholm, Arthur W., 1980-1988 (Box 21, Folder 483)
  - Lippincott, Horace Mather, 1953-1954 (Box 21, Folder 484)
  - Lipson, Leon, 1968-1981 (Box 21, Folder 485)
  - Livergood, Norman D., 1959-1979 (Box 21, Folder 486)
  - Livingstone, Richard, 1952-1956, undated (Box 21, Folder 487)
  - Lochner, Richard P., 1936-1949 (Box 21, Folder 488)
  - Locke, Edwin, 1970-1976 (Box 21, Folder 489)
  - Lofstrom, Edward V., 1962-1988 (Box 21, Folder 490-492)
    See also: box 1, folder 1-5
  - Lopez, Robert, 1966-1987 (Box 21, Folder 493)
  - Lottinville, Savoie, 1980-1989 (Box 21, Folder 494)
  - Lovejoy, Arthur D., 1948, undated (Box 22, Folder 495)
  - Lowry, Howard, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 496)